拯救世界，那又如何
反正它又不會突然消失
I saved a row, even though
I know it won't be taken
我原以為你們不會走
我錯得如此離譜
I thought at first you'd never go
I was so mistaken
大家都說，生命總有終點
I was told life won't last forever
但我已超越了那條界線
But I've gone beyond the marker
他會怎麼做？
會有何感受？
What's one to do?
How's one to feel?
又何去何從
當他沒法打開心胸？
Where's one to go
when their heart won't open?
遠在天邊
卻唾手可及
So far away
Yet so nearby
彷彿誰還在看著
我的一舉一動
Feels as if someone's still
watching over me
所以，我希望
So, here's to hoping
如今，我已不想面對
生活的各種驚喜
Nowadays, I pick and choose
my circumstances
我不相信，命運有那
我幻想的第二次機會
I don't believe that fate is up
for giving second chances
如果我沒想錯，時間永不停歇
If I'm right, time goes on forever
感覺還有好多
值得回憶
Feels like there's so much
to remember
他會怎麼做？
會有何感受？
What's one to do?
How's one to feel?
又何去何從
當他沒法打開心胸？
Where's one to go
when their heart won't open?
遠在天邊
卻唾手可及
So far away
Yet so nearby
彷彿誰還在看著
我的一舉一動
Feels as if someone's still
watching over me
所以，我...
So, here's to...
...緊握著渺小的希望
緊跟著時間的腳步
...holding on to a little faith
keeping up with the present day
好好珍惜
我的這些朋友們
standing well with
the friends I made
同時確保
我不會就此迷路
and making sure
that I don't lose my way
他會怎麼做？
會有何感受？
What's one to do?
How's one to feel?
又何去何從
當他沒法打開心胸？
Where's one to go
when their heart won't open?
遠在天邊
卻唾手可及
So far away
Yet so nearby
彷彿誰還在看著
我的一舉一動
Feels as if someone's still
watching over me
所以，我希望
So, here's to hoping